[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which kangaroo species is the largest on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Red Kangaroo", "incorrect_answers": ["Antilopine Kangaroo", "Western Grey Kangaroo", "Eastern Grey Kangaroo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 14th Century, Moscow replaced this city as the cultural center of Russia.", "correct_answer": "Kiev", "incorrect_answers": ["Leningrad", "Riga", "St. Petersburg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the minimum ocean water temperature required for a tropical cyclone to form?", "correct_answer": "80 degrees Fahrenheit", "incorrect_answers": ["87 degrees Fahrenheit", "77 degrees Fahrenheit", "93 degrees Fahrenheit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the original Disney script  Bambi was supposed to be shot by the hunters instead of the mother.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I sat back down on my bed and looked around my room. This triggered my autophobia. What was I afraid of?", "correct_answer": "Being alone", "incorrect_answers": ["Being late for work", "Dust", "An unmade bed"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "WWII is undoubtedly the bloodiest war. This is the number of fatalities it caused.", "correct_answer": "56.4 million", "incorrect_answers": ["44.0 million", "71.8 million", "27.3 million"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who  wrote the concertos called The Four Seasons?", "correct_answer": "Vivaldi", "incorrect_answers": ["Schumann", "Mozart", "Corelli"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The dog, that appeared as Toto in the movie The Wizard of Oz, belonged to actress Judy Garland in real life as well as in the film.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the first computer game?", "correct_answer": "Tennis For Two", "incorrect_answers": ["Tetris", "Myst", "Pong"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The epidermis is very rich in blood vessels.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Solar System celestial bodys revolution around the Sun takes 248 years?", "correct_answer": "Pluto", "incorrect_answers": ["Saturn", "Neptune", "Uranus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which European Union member the native people make up only 60% of the total population?", "correct_answer": "Latvia", "incorrect_answers": ["Poland", "Austria", "France"]}]